<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>education on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in education on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:06:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Casualties in the Information War</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction People need to understand and agree with the goal of a system. If people ignore the goal of a system, then the system is assuredly being wasteful and counterproductive.
Goals In the introduction to The Goal by Eli Goldratt, he defines science as a method for creating explanations. But he clearly distinguishes science from knowledge. Eli Goldratt requires knowledge to be able to make our world better and life more fulfilling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorting Myself Out</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</guid>
      <description>Supposedly there is this thing called &amp;ldquo;the meaning crisis&amp;rdquo; and many people are nihilists. Who knew? What does that even mean? Maybe I can help.
I believe the hell you are in is an opportunity to develop your stack of skills and try to become an important part of the story by which hell is transformed into heaven. I believe the smallest changes done with the right spirit can have the biggest impact as the chain of events ripple through space-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising is Fishing for People</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</guid>
      <description>I think it is interesting that Jesus&amp;rsquo; first disciples were fishermen who were asked to fish for people. You can have the best product, service, or idea and people will not know about it unless you are able to be successful with your advertising strategies. An advertisement is an attempt to capture a person&amp;rsquo;s attention. Our attention is extremely valuable and every good advertiser knows this.
As a software engineer in organizations which must protect information, I have done security training which taught me how to avoid becoming an attack vector within an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do Sensemaking</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 07:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</guid>
      <description>We can solve the sensemaking problem.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarianism is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The truth is that very few people are correct in their ideology because they do not understand human nature and our universal fallibility.
 I was a utilitarian when I was young. This means that I believed the means justify the ends. I would tell a lie if I could justify it. But I also know that I believed things which were wrong. I believed I had discovered a perpetual energy design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Security</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</guid>
      <description>I will criticize an immoral Republican view and then I will criticize an immoral Democrat view. My morality assessments depend on whether or not a person&amp;rsquo;s behavior is in alignment with my ideology.
Introduction In a dream I am given a test. If everyone in the class picks the first choice then everyone gets a perfect score. But if anyone picks the second choice and does all the work then everyone who did the first choice will get half of a perfect score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christian</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</guid>
      <description>There were mistakes in the original post and edits have been made. Please let me know if you find any mistakes.
 I am not convinced that being Christian is the best. My concern about Christians is that they are ultimately willing to sacrifice their life on Earth because their reward is in heaven. The Christian is at odds with the Anti-Christian who does not want to sacrifice their life on Earth because they do not believe their reward is in heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misinterpretations</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</guid>
      <description>We humans let ideas and interpretations of words slip into our mind without thinking critically. And if we are not willing to question our beliefs then we remain stuck with ignorance and confusion. But if we question our beliefs then we have the opportunity to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a Thought Leader</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</guid>
      <description>“Bernays&amp;rsquo; thesis is that &amp;ldquo;invisible&amp;rdquo; people who create knowledge and propaganda rule over the masses, with a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response.” - Wikipedia
 In the current age of the internet, there is no longer a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response. Where there was once a monopoly there is now an oligarchy of thought leaders where each person in that oligarchy is a gatekeeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Sense Making</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</guid>
      <description>Our malfunctioning sense making organ is the fundamental sickness we can all be trying to heal.
We can measure our love based on our attention. Our attention is fundamental to our sense making. And so our love and our sense making are related individually and collectively.
 Love everyone  Love by proximity Love by relevance Be honest.    Love everyone. One of my claims is that a properly functioning sense making organ should be loving and able to prioritize information based on its relevance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minerval Arts</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</guid>
      <description>I would pay money to see good conversations happening because good conversations are absent in our world. I believe other people would also be interested in paying money to see good conversations happening. Gandhi taught to be the change you wish to see and my goal is to create a place where good conversations happen.
I have created a Patreon account which allows subscribers to gain attention on my Discord server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Humans</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</guid>
      <description>I have completed the first part of Managing Humans by Michael Lopp. I think the most interesting chapter in the book is titled &amp;ldquo;Titles are Toxic&amp;rdquo;. Lopp suggests titles are toxic because they attempt to place value on humans who are beautiful snowflakes. He thinks titles are as useless as business cards and resumes. And I tend to agree with his sentiment.
A general problem I see in organizations is that people keep their role if they are “good enough”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement with Eric Weinstein and Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>How do people with good ideas and without power teach people with power who could best help make the ideas into our reality when there is no obvious way to even begin the conversation? People with good ideas and motivations need to be able to see a gate which can be opened for them and the paths which lead to that gate. What I have been trying to do is imagine gates and paths by which I am able to reach, teach, and learn with other people who are willing and able to solve important problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Encounter Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this with Eric Weinstein in mind. But this general approach to learning and cooperating with a large community can be implemented by anyone who has a sufficiently large following. I am excited to see people trying to figure out how to improve the sense making organ for a large community of people.
You have realized that you need to put forth some effort having conversations with new people who have new ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>