<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>education on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in education on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/santa-claus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/santa-claus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I remember being a child and having a girl tell me she knew who Santa Claus was but she wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to tell me. I begged her until she finally told me everyone&amp;rsquo;s parents are pretending to be Santa Claus. She was a Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witness.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe everyone was participating in a grand conspiracy, but I also had to begin my journey as a practicing skeptic and investigator. I remember when all the pieces came together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minerval Arts</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is an invitation to practice minerval arts with me or anyone you can find who is willing to participate. Minerval arts is a friendly battle of minds and ideas with an ultimate goal of increasing awareness for the practitioners and observers. If everyone practiced and appreciated minerval arts we would have our best chance at peace on Earth because we would have our best chance at optimally informed decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensemaking in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sensemaking-in-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sensemaking-in-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of my first posts was about a universal problem I called the Human Resource Problem (HRP). If the universal problem is HRP then the universal solution is Sensemaking.
I want to point our attention at our healthcare problems and attempt to shine light on some more specific human resource problems and sensemaking solutions in our healthcare system.
Health Problems We all experience healthcare problems in our lives. And the people who are licensed and approved to provide healthcare solutions to our healthcare problems make mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Biden Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/president-biden-mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/president-biden-mistakes/</guid>
      <description>Pointing out President&amp;rsquo;s mistakes could be a fun hobby.
Executive Order on Requiring Coronavirus Disease 2019 Vaccination for Federal Employees A link to the executive order on whitehouse.gov and a link to a copy in my repository.
What is President Biden&amp;rsquo;s Stated Primary Goal?  halt the spread of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19)  What is President Biden&amp;rsquo;s Stated Secondary Goal?  the health and safety of the Federal workforce and the efficiency of the civil service  How should these goals be accomplished?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transparency</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/transparency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/transparency/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
Introduction My intent is to identify the ideal scenario. I realize that our present is not ideal and we should work towards the ideal incrementally.
My claim is that there are certain individuals who are so spiritually mature that they could have their lives recorded and streamed to the world as evidence of their righteousness and qualification as the elect leaders of our world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Every time I am about to share information with other people I can transform that information into a blog post like I am doing now. When I create a blog post, I get to own my content and control my content. I can then share a link to my post on all of my social media networks. I can also update my blog post so that all of the links I shared get updated as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Words For Good</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/using-words-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/using-words-for-good/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
Words can be pointers to ideas, but they can also be pointers to stories. Stories and ideas are very different. Stories can be visualized in the mind. Those visualizations can produce emotions. And like the dog who is trained to salivate at the sound of a bell, a human can be trained to love or hate at the sound of a word.
During my mandatory training as a child in the United States, the word racism was referenced in stories about innocent people being enslaved or strangled to death with ropes tied to trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Attention</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-attention/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
Popular people with good goals must:
 try to respect everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention. appreciate the importance and potential of people and their attention. remember that a person&amp;rsquo;s attention changes over time.  Attention is Scarce Humans have limited attention. I remember talking about this situation with my wife when we thought about bringing an additional human into the world. Each time we add another member into our family, the amount of attention we are able to give each family member decreases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-goal/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
My Goal My goal has been to help create peace on Earth. With that goal in mind I have thought about prerequisites like &amp;ldquo;providing an abundance of clean water to all people without forcing them to do things they do not want to do&amp;rdquo;. Part of the problem of providing clean water is related to waste management and many other problems. Ultimately, our ability to accomplish the goal is based on our ability to cooperate with other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casualties in the Information War</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
You can see the git commit history here. I was encouraged to improve this post here. Thanks Max!
Introduction The authorities should not be trusted when they are not willing nor able to solve problems which make our world better. I have encountered evidence which indicates that FACEBOOK and Science Feedback are being misleading and should not be trusted to help solve important problems and make our world better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorting Myself Out</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</guid>
      <description>Supposedly there is this thing called &amp;ldquo;the meaning crisis&amp;rdquo; and many people are nihilists. Who knew? What does that even mean? Maybe I can help.
I believe the hell you are in is an opportunity to develop your stack of skills and try to become an important part of the story by which hell is transformed into heaven. I believe the smallest changes done with the right spirit can have the biggest impact as the chain of events ripple through space-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising is Fishing for People</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</guid>
      <description>I think it is interesting that Jesus&#39; first disciples were fishermen who were asked to fish for people. You can have the best product, service, or idea and people will not know about it unless you are able to be successful with your advertising strategies. An advertisement is an attempt to capture a person&amp;rsquo;s attention. Our attention is extremely valuable and every good advertiser knows this.
As a software engineer in organizations which must protect information, I have done security training which taught me how to avoid becoming an attack vector within an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do Sensemaking</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 07:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</guid>
      <description>Sensemaking is a process of learning and teaching. Learning and teaching requires constant feedback. As individuals, we need to appreciate feedback from others and we need to be willing to give feedback to others. We need to create opportunities for others to give us feedback. And we need to reach out to people who claim to be interested in working towards common goals.
Receiving Feedback If you want to receive feedback, make sure people can contact you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarianism is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The truth is that very few people are correct in their ideology because they do not understand human nature and our universal fallibility.
 I was a utilitarian when I was young. This means that I believed the means justify the ends. I would tell a lie if I could justify it. But I also know that I believed things which were wrong. I believed I had discovered a perpetual energy design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Security</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</guid>
      <description>I will criticize an immoral Republican view and then I will criticize an immoral Democrat view. My morality assessments depend on whether or not a person&amp;rsquo;s behavior is in alignment with my ideology.
Introduction In a dream I am given a test. If everyone in the class picks the first choice then everyone gets a perfect score. But if anyone picks the second choice and does all the work then everyone who did the first choice will get half of a perfect score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christian</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</guid>
      <description>as of 10/01/2021, I identify as a Christian   There were mistakes in the original post and edits have been made. Please let me know if you find any mistakes.
 I am not convinced that being Christian is the best. My concern about Christians is that they are ultimately willing to sacrifice their life on Earth because their reward is in heaven. The Christian is at odds with the Anti-Christian who does not want to sacrifice their life on Earth because they do not believe their reward is in heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misinterpretations</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</guid>
      <description>We humans let ideas and interpretations of words slip into our mind without thinking critically. And if we are not willing to question our beliefs then we remain stuck with ignorance and confusion. But if we question our beliefs then we have the opportunity to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a Thought Leader</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</guid>
      <description>“Bernays&#39; thesis is that &amp;ldquo;invisible&amp;rdquo; people who create knowledge and propaganda rule over the masses, with a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response.” - Wikipedia
 In the current age of the internet, there is no longer a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response. Where there was once a monopoly there is now an oligarchy of thought leaders where each person in that oligarchy is a gatekeeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Sense Making</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</guid>
      <description>Our malfunctioning sense making organ is the fundamental sickness we can all be trying to heal.
We can measure our love based on our attention. Our attention is fundamental to our sense making. And so our love and our sense making are related individually and collectively.
 Love everyone  Love by proximity Love by relevance Be honest.    Love everyone. One of my claims is that a properly functioning sense making organ should be loving and able to prioritize information based on its relevance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Environmental Policy Response</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</guid>
      <description>This is a response to Aaron Harburg&amp;rsquo;s Data and Environmental Policy.
 Environmental Law is predicated on the assumption that the government can effectively motivate its citizens to perform or abstain from certain activities.
 All laws which criminalize behavior are coercive and part of the failing justice system.
 The question is how incentives and punishments should be used to achieve and ensure the greatest effect.
 That’s a good question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Humans</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</guid>
      <description>I have completed the first part of Managing Humans by Michael Lopp. I think the most interesting chapter in the book is titled &amp;ldquo;Titles are Toxic&amp;rdquo;. Lopp suggests titles are toxic because they attempt to place value on humans who are beautiful snowflakes. He thinks titles are as useless as business cards and resumes. And I tend to agree with his sentiment.
A general problem I see in organizations is that people keep their role if they are “good enough”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement with Eric Weinstein and Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>How do people with good ideas and without power teach people with power who could best help make the ideas into our reality when there is no obvious way to even begin the conversation? People with good ideas and motivations need to be able to see a gate which can be opened for them and the paths which lead to that gate. What I have been trying to do is imagine gates and paths by which I am able to reach, teach, and learn with other people who are willing and able to solve important problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Encounter Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this with Eric Weinstein in mind. But this general approach to learning and cooperating with a large community can be implemented by anyone who has a sufficiently large following. I am excited to see people trying to figure out how to improve the sense making organ for a large community of people.
You have realized that you need to put forth some effort having conversations with new people who have new ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
