<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>justice on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/justice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in justice on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sparking Innovation Through Fair and Transparent Competitions</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sparking-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sparking-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced world, competitions have become a powerful driving force behind innovation and progress. They provide a platform for individuals and organizations to showcase their talents and ideas, pushing the boundaries of what is possible. However, the integrity of these competitions can sometimes be called into question, making it crucial to establish a transparent and unbiased judging system. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the importance of fair competitions in fostering innovation and propose a novel judging system to ensure transparency and trust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Environmental Policy Response</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</guid>
      <description>This is a response to Aaron Harburg&amp;rsquo;s Data and Environmental Policy.
 Environmental Law is predicated on the assumption that the government can effectively motivate its citizens to perform or abstain from certain activities.
 All laws which criminalize behavior are coercive and part of the failing justice system.
 The question is how incentives and punishments should be used to achieve and ensure the greatest effect.
 That’s a good question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and Government</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 08:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</guid>
      <description>What is religion? I like the meaning of the word religion which corresponds with the idea that Jordan Peterson introduced me to regarding our actions. When asked if he believes in God, he responds that he lives his life as if God exists. I think our actions are the essential part of our religious belief. I think it was the Christian James who taught faith without works is dead. I think our work is vital and defines our religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending the War on Drugs</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</guid>
      <description>Why was the War on Drugs started? If I steelman the arguments for the idea of controlling substances, I would imagine a different time without the internet when people had access to less information. I am young enough to remember researching cannabis and psilocybin on the internet before I experimented with those substances. There was a time when it was much harder to do your research in order to understand a substance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
