<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>imagination on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/imagination/</link>
    <description>Recent content in imagination on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/imagination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Effective Altruism Criticisms</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/effective-altruism-criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/effective-altruism-criticism/</guid>
      <description>I recently learned about the Effective Altruism (EA) organization who has a competition with incentives for people to help with their error correction. The strategy of a competition and the goal of doing error correction is extremely important in my mind.
My criticisms are generally related to attention and technology because I believe attention is the most valuable resource in the world and technology can help us manage our attention better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metapolitech</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/metapolitech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/metapolitech/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;m now old enough to be President of the United States of America (POTUS). The only reason I am considering running for POTUS is because the people who usually try to be POTUS are unable to solve the most fundamental problems we face. My hope is that I can share information about actions the reader can perform to participate in our transformation.
Corruption, Trustworthiness, and Funding We are all corrupted people to one degree or another deserving limited trustworthiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Tech</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/food/</guid>
      <description>Food Tech A conversation about food can lead towards a conversation about socialism and capitalism. This conversation about socialism and capitalism can be temporarily avoided by focusing on technology which could be used within many different economic systems.
The food technology I&amp;rsquo;d like to use would allow me to receive the best affordable food with the least amount of effort. Note that my wife would prefer a slightly different food technology where the ingredients are delivered to her alongside recipes used to make meals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/global-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/global-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>The Convective Heat Engine (CHE) is the primary infrastructure for a sustainable city design which can protect against drought, famine, and climate change. It can be used to capture thousands of tons of carbon per year while providing a reliable supply of water, shelter, and electricity for a population of 100,000 people.
The latest estimated price of a CHE is $6 billion. The price tag per ton of carbon being sequestered looks expensive at first glance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness Becomes a Felony</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/homelessness-becomes-a-felony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/homelessness-becomes-a-felony/</guid>
      <description>Tennessee is about to become the first U.S. state to make it a felony to camp on local public property such as parks.
  The law requires that violators receive at least 24 hours notice before an arrest. The felony charge is punishable by up to six years in prison and the loss of voting rights.
 Six years and the loss of voting rights seem excessive to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsource Mail</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/crowdsource-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/crowdsource-mail/</guid>
      <description>After many years of trying to find a group to help, I was introduced to Jacob Faturechi who shared an experimental idea to fix distributed cognition (or cognitive outsourcing). We call it crowdsource mail.
This could be code named &amp;ldquo;Project Jethro&amp;rdquo;.
Exodus 18 Moses&#39; father-in-law is named Jethro
 Moses immediately listened to his father-in-law and did all that he had said. Moses chose capable men out of all Israel and appointed them heads over the people, as chiefs of thousands, chiefs of hundreds, chiefs of fifties, and chiefs of tens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/side-projects/</guid>
      <description> Truth My Religion Convective Heat Engine (CHE) Crowdsource Mail Secure Card Payments The Space Elevator Minerval Arts  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Transparency for Peace on Earth</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>This post has had changes.
When our work is recorded and shared with the world we are facilitating the same education process which happens when open source software engineers build tools you are using to read this post right now.
Transparency By the end of this post, I will begin explaining new ways of implementing limited transparency into society.
If enough work is done in the full light of transparency technologies, we would end world hunger and all threats of war within 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A World Without Hunger</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</guid>
      <description>The first person I have known to take autonomous agriculture technology seriously is Douglas Mallette, founder of Cybernated Farm Systems.
We can technically feed the world with autonomous agriculture technology which eventually requires no human labor.
It has been said that you can give a man a fish and feed him for a day. It has been said that you can teach a man to fish and feed him the rest of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
