<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Futurism on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/futurism/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Futurism on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/futurism/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Transparency for Peace on Earth</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>When our work is recorded and shared with the world we are facilitating the same education process which happens when open source software engineers build tools you are using to read this post right now.
Transparency By the end of this post, I will begin explaining new ways of integrating transparency into society.
If all work was done in the full light of transparency technologies, we would end world hunger and all threats of war within 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A World Without Hunger</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</guid>
      <description>The first person I have known to take autonomous agriculture technology seriously is Douglas Mallette, founder of Cybernated Farm Systems.
We can technically feed the world with autonomous agriculture technology which eventually requires no human labor.
It has been said that you can give a man a fish and feed him for a day. It has been said that you can teach a man to fish and feed him the rest of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>