<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>government on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/government/</link>
    <description>Recent content in government on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:21:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/government/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Helping The Greatest Intentions</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/helping-the-greatest-intentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/helping-the-greatest-intentions/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
The energy I invest in this thought space is dedicated toward serving the greatest intentions. This ultimately means I am willing to put myself in service to others with my energy.
The process of creating peace on Earth and solving the Human Resource Problem is directly related to increasing people&amp;rsquo;s attention to the right ideas. One such idea is platforming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Transparency for Peace on Earth</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>This post has had changes.
When our work is recorded and shared with the world we are facilitating the same education process which happens when open source software engineers build tools you are using to read this post right now.
Transparency By the end of this post, I will begin explaining new ways of implementing limited transparency into society.
If enough work is done in the full light of transparency technologies, we would end world hunger and all threats of war within 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Environmental Policy Response</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</guid>
      <description>This is a response to Aaron Harburg&amp;rsquo;s Data and Environmental Policy.
 Environmental Law is predicated on the assumption that the government can effectively motivate its citizens to perform or abstain from certain activities.
 All laws which criminalize behavior are coercive and part of the failing justice system.
 The question is how incentives and punishments should be used to achieve and ensure the greatest effect.
 That’s a good question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and Government</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 08:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</guid>
      <description>What is religion? I like the meaning of the word religion which corresponds with the idea that Jordan Peterson introduced me to regarding our actions. When asked if he believes in God, he responds that he lives his life as if God exists. I think our actions are the essential part of our religious belief. I think it was the Christian James who taught faith without works is dead. I think our work is vital and defines our religion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
