<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 07:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do Sensemaking</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 07:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</guid>
      <description>We can solve the sensemaking problem.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarianism is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The truth is that very few people are correct in their ideology because they do not understand human nature and our universal fallibility.
 I was a utilitarian when I was young. This means that I believed the means justify the ends. I would tell a lie if I could justify it. But I also know that I believed things which were wrong. I believed I had discovered a perpetual energy design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Security</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</guid>
      <description>I will criticize an immoral Republican view and then I will criticize an immoral Democrat view. My morality assessments depend on whether or not a person&amp;rsquo;s behavior is in alignment with my ideology.
Introduction In a dream I am given a test. If everyone in the class picks the first choice then everyone gets a perfect score. But if anyone picks the second choice and does all the work then everyone who did the first choice will get half of a perfect score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christian</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</guid>
      <description>There were mistakes in the original post and edits have been made. Please let me know if you find any mistakes.
 I am not convinced that being Christian is the best. My concern about Christians is that they are ultimately willing to sacrifice their life on Earth because their reward is in heaven. The Christian is at odds with the Anti-Christian who does not want to sacrifice their life on Earth because they do not believe their reward is in heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misinterpretations</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</guid>
      <description>We humans let ideas and interpretations of words slip into our mind without thinking critically. And if we are not willing to question our beliefs then we remain stuck with ignorance and confusion. But if we question our beliefs then we have the opportunity to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Sense Making</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</guid>
      <description>Our malfunctioning sense making organ is the fundamental sickness we can all be trying to heal.
We can measure our love based on our attention. Our attention is fundamental to our sense making. And so our love and our sense making are related individually and collectively.
 Love everyone  Love by proximity Love by relevance Be honest.    Love everyone. One of my claims is that a properly functioning sense making organ should be loving and able to prioritize information based on its relevance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win My Vote in 2020</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-win-my-vote-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-win-my-vote-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking about who I should vote for POTUS in 2020.
I would vote for the candidate who abandons the mainstream and supports new platforms for information distribution and sense making. Twitter and Facebook are aweful. And I don&amp;rsquo;t think the candidate should just go over to Parler. Ideally the POTUS would use an open source Mastadon server or some other federated social media platform which allows for decentralization and owning your own data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>