<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 04:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vampires and Zombies</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/vampires-and-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/vampires-and-zombies/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Summary The monsters are within us. The battle starts within and never ends.
Introduction We get to figure this out together and create peace on Earth as we solve the biggest problem and embody the best answer.
Trained Responses We often respond to stimuli like Pavlov&amp;rsquo;s dog who was trained to salivate at the sound of a bell but we do it with words. This is the mindless zombie within us who does not want to change our views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Engineer</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-engineer/</guid>
      <description>I told Karen Wong, with The Meaning Code YouTube channel, that I would write in preparation for our meeting later today and so here it is. I gave her a list of topics which had been on my mind and she expressed interest in praxeology and perspectivism.
Praxeology is the study of action and is primary for me. And perspectivism is the study of the impact of perspective upon action. But while reading about these words and taking notes (see below) I remembered Haidt&amp;rsquo;s elephant and elephant rider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Less Wrong Views</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/less-wrong-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/less-wrong-views/</guid>
      <description>mistake 1: no goals If we do not aim at targets then we have no way of learning from our mistakes because we have no outcomes to use in the assessment of our actions.
mistake 2: wrong goals If we harm people in the pursuit of our goals then we can get better at choosing our targets.
mistake 3: too easy goals If we aim at easy targets we will never accomplish anything of difficulty and may never learn the importance of cooperation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research and Development</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/research-and-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/research-and-development/</guid>
      <description>The goal is peace on Earth. Every moment can be inspected as we seek the ideal which leads toward peace.
  The light side of the force increases opportunities for a healthy life:
  The process of creation is the alternating process of reaping and sowing.
  The reaping process (alternative words: distillation or harvesting) extracts the substances.
  Water is the building block for life and peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minerval Arts</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/minerval-arts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is an invitation to practice minerval arts with me or anyone you can find who is willing to participate. Minerval arts is a friendly battle of minds and ideas with an ultimate goal of increasing awareness for the practitioners and observers. If everyone practiced and appreciated minerval arts we would have our best chance at peace on Earth because we would have our best chance at optimally informed decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strange Birds</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/strange-birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/strange-birds/</guid>
      <description>Because most people don&amp;rsquo;t start at the end, I decided to re-arrange the content accordingly. If you reverse the order of the content you may notice how the exercise flows into the conclusion.
Conclusion I truly apologize to anyone I may have offended because of my lack of patience-gentleness-kindness. This process of expressing myself in this blog post has been therapeutic for me. I have belittled myself a little more and exercised my demon a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Claus</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/santa-claus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/santa-claus/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I remember being a child and having a girl tell me she knew who Santa Claus was but she wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to tell me. I begged her until she finally told me everyone&amp;rsquo;s parents are pretending to be Santa Claus. She was a Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witness.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe everyone was participating in a grand conspiracy, but I also had to begin my journey as a practicing skeptic and investigator. I remember when all the pieces came together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discontent</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/discontent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/discontent/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;m a problem solver. G-d taught me to see through bullshit and get to the point.
A friend mentioned feeling a tinge of discontentment. My first thought was about the word &amp;ldquo;content&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m creating content right now in order to satisfy my feeling of discontent. And my feeling of discontentment was given to me by my friend expressing his feeling for which I am grateful because sharing the feeling is the way our relationship can grow as we learn to deal with stress together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensemaking in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sensemaking-in-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sensemaking-in-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One of my first posts was about a universal problem I called the Human Resource Problem (HRP). If the universal problem is HRP then the universal solution is Sensemaking.
I want to point our attention at our healthcare problems and attempt to shine light on some more specific human resource problems and sensemaking solutions in our healthcare system.
Health Problems We all experience healthcare problems in our lives. And the people who are licensed and approved to provide healthcare solutions to our healthcare problems make mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Problems and Solutions</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/healthcare-problems-and-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/healthcare-problems-and-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
Problem: Limited Supply of Healthcare Resources Ignorance The general problem of ignorance in healthcare demands the general solution of sensemaking in healthcare.
COVID-19 People report the COVID-19 pandemic leads to hospitals being overcrowded with COVID-19 patients which strains the healthcare system.
Short-term Solution: Allow Assisted Suicides  A better choice of words would be &amp;ldquo;improved hospice services&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;allow assisted suicides&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Biden Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/president-biden-mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/president-biden-mistakes/</guid>
      <description>Pointing out President&amp;rsquo;s mistakes could be a fun hobby.
Executive Order on Requiring Coronavirus Disease 2019 Vaccination for Federal Employees A link to the executive order on whitehouse.gov and a link to a copy in my repository.
What is President Biden&amp;rsquo;s Stated Primary Goal?  halt the spread of coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19)  What is President Biden&amp;rsquo;s Stated Secondary Goal?  the health and safety of the Federal workforce and the efficiency of the civil service  How should these goals be accomplished?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsource Mail</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/crowdsource-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/crowdsource-mail/</guid>
      <description>After many years of trying to find a group to help, I was introduced to Jacob Faturechi who shared an experimental idea to fix distributed cognition (or cognitive outsourcing). We call it crowdsource mail.
This could be code named &amp;ldquo;Project Jethro&amp;rdquo;.
Exodus 18 Moses&amp;rsquo; father-in-law is named Jethro
 Moses immediately listened to his father-in-law and did all that he had said. Moses chose capable men out of all Israel and appointed them heads over the people, as chiefs of thousands, chiefs of hundreds, chiefs of fifties, and chiefs of tens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Climate Change</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/global-climate-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/global-climate-change/</guid>
      <description>After many years of trying to find a group to help, I was introduced to Jason Delport who shared an idea to solve climate change problems with the Convective Heat Engine (CHE).
The CHE can transform deserts into a land of abundance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/side-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/side-projects/</guid>
      <description> Truth My Religion Convective Heat Engine (CHE) Crowdsource Mail Secure Card Payments The Space Elevator Minerval Arts  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/truth/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
 What are my goals?  I learn. I give intent. I invite feedback. I give progress. I give outcomes. I seek peace.    What is Truth? Words are symbols and symbols can attempt to point at the Truth. The territory is real and the map attempts to point at the territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/government/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/government/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
 What are my goals?  I learn. I give intent. I invite feedback. I give progress. I give outcomes. I seek peace.    What is government? Government is a system which has inputs, outputs, functions, and goals.
What is government corruption? The perception of government corruption emerges when people disagree with government activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reminders</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/reminders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/reminders/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
If given the opportunity,
 cooperate observe attention lead by example be honest be intentional be healthy be strategic be humble be curious be patient be grateful be peaceful be playful  Religious Our religion is how we act in the world. Our actions should align with nature.
 I practice grounding my attention in the present by giving my attention to my breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping The Greatest Intentions</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/helping-the-greatest-intentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 05:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/helping-the-greatest-intentions/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
The energy I invest in this thought space is dedicated toward serving the greatest intentions. This ultimately means I am willing to put myself in service to others with my energy.
The process of creating peace on Earth and solving the Human Resource Problem is directly related to increasing people&amp;rsquo;s attention to the right ideas. One such idea is platforming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Transparency for Peace on Earth</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/limited-transparency-for-peace-on-earth/</guid>
      <description>This post has had changes.
When our work is recorded and shared with the world we are facilitating the same education process which happens when open source software engineers build tools you are using to read this post right now.
Transparency By the end of this post, I will begin explaining new ways of implementing limited transparency into society.
If enough work is done in the full light of transparency technologies, we would end world hunger and all threats of war within 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transparency</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/transparency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/transparency/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer practicing a relationship with the Greatest Intentions
Serious content should have version control with historical changes.
Introduction My intent is to identify the ideal scenario. I realize that our present is not ideal and we should work towards the ideal incrementally.
My claim is that there are certain individuals who are so spiritually mature that they could have their lives recorded and streamed to the world as evidence of their righteousness and qualification as the elect leaders of our world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/content-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/content-creation/</guid>
      <description>Every time I am about to share information with other people I can transform that information into a blog post like I am doing now. When I create a blog post, I get to own my content and control my content. I can then share a link to my post on all of my social media networks. I can also update my blog post so that all of the links I shared get updated as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Words For Good</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/using-words-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/using-words-for-good/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
Words can be pointers to ideas, but they can also be pointers to stories. Stories and ideas are very different. Stories can be visualized in the mind. Those visualizations can produce emotions. And like the dog who is trained to salivate at the sound of a bell, a human can be trained to love or hate at the sound of a word.
During my mandatory training as a child in the United States, the word racism was referenced in stories about innocent people being enslaved or strangled to death with ropes tied to trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Attention</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-attention/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
Popular people with good goals must:
 try to respect everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention. appreciate the importance and potential of people and their attention. remember that a person&amp;rsquo;s attention changes over time.  Attention is Scarce Humans have limited attention. I remember talking about this situation with my wife when we thought about bringing an additional human into the world. Each time we add another member into our family, the amount of attention we are able to give each family member decreases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-goal/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
My Goal My goal has been to help create peace on Earth. With that goal in mind I have thought about prerequisites like &amp;ldquo;providing an abundance of clean water to all people without forcing them to do things they do not want to do&amp;rdquo;. Part of the problem of providing clean water is related to waste management and many other problems. Ultimately, our ability to accomplish the goal is based on our ability to cooperate with other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casualties in the Information War</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:06:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/casualties-in-the-information-war/</guid>
      <description>Written by Gavin Palmer
You can see the git commit history here. I was encouraged to improve this post here. Thanks Max!
Introduction The authorities should not be trusted when they are not willing nor able to solve problems which make our world better. I have encountered evidence which indicates that FACEBOOK and Science Feedback are being misleading and should not be trusted to help solve important problems and make our world better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorting Myself Out</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/sorting-myself-out/</guid>
      <description>Supposedly there is this thing called &amp;ldquo;the meaning crisis&amp;rdquo; and many people are nihilists. Who knew? What does that even mean? Maybe I can help.
I believe the hell you are in is an opportunity to develop your stack of skills and try to become an important part of the story by which hell is transformed into heaven. I believe the smallest changes done with the right spirit can have the biggest impact as the chain of events ripple through space-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertising is Fishing for People</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/advertising-is-fishing-for-people/</guid>
      <description>I think it is interesting that Jesus&amp;rsquo; first disciples were fishermen who were asked to fish for people. You can have the best product, service, or idea and people will not know about it unless you are able to be successful with your advertising strategies. An advertisement is an attempt to capture a person&amp;rsquo;s attention. Our attention is extremely valuable and every good advertiser knows this.
As a software engineer in organizations which must protect information, I have done security training which taught me how to avoid becoming an attack vector within an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do Sensemaking</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 07:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-do-sensemaking/</guid>
      <description>Sensemaking is a process of learning and teaching. Learning and teaching requires constant feedback. As individuals, we need to appreciate feedback from others and we need to be willing to give feedback to others. We need to create opportunities for others to give us feedback. And we need to reach out to people who claim to be interested in working towards common goals.
Receiving Feedback If you want to receive feedback, make sure people can contact you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarianism is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The truth is that very few people are correct in their ideology because they do not understand human nature and our universal fallibility.
 I was a utilitarian when I was young. This means that I believed the means justify the ends. I would tell a lie if I could justify it. But I also know that I believed things which were wrong. I believed I had discovered a perpetual energy design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheating in Elections</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheating-in-elections/</guid>
      <description>The thing we should do now is improve our election system and have another election in those areas where witnesses have reported illegal activity.
 I heard someone say &amp;ldquo;There is no proof of election fraud and even if there was election fraud against Donald Trump it would be a good thing.&amp;rdquo; This captures much of the sentiment of people who wanted to see Donald Trump lose in 2020. And it is not hard to believe that people tried to cheat in order to defeat Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Security</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</guid>
      <description>I will criticize an immoral Republican view and then I will criticize an immoral Democrat view. My morality assessments depend on whether or not a person&amp;rsquo;s behavior is in alignment with my ideology.
Introduction In a dream I am given a test. If everyone in the class picks the first choice then everyone gets a perfect score. But if anyone picks the second choice and does all the work then everyone who did the first choice will get half of a perfect score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christian</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</guid>
      <description>as of 10/01/2021, I identify as a Christian   There were mistakes in the original post and edits have been made. Please let me know if you find any mistakes.
 I am not convinced that being Christian is the best. My concern about Christians is that they are ultimately willing to sacrifice their life on Earth because their reward is in heaven. The Christian is at odds with the Anti-Christian who does not want to sacrifice their life on Earth because they do not believe their reward is in heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misinterpretations</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</guid>
      <description>We humans let ideas and interpretations of words slip into our mind without thinking critically. And if we are not willing to question our beliefs then we remain stuck with ignorance and confusion. But if we question our beliefs then we have the opportunity to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a Thought Leader</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-be-a-better-thought-leader/</guid>
      <description>“Bernays&amp;rsquo; thesis is that &amp;ldquo;invisible&amp;rdquo; people who create knowledge and propaganda rule over the masses, with a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response.” - Wikipedia
 In the current age of the internet, there is no longer a monopoly on the power to shape thoughts, values, and citizen response. Where there was once a monopoly there is now an oligarchy of thought leaders where each person in that oligarchy is a gatekeeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Sense Making</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</guid>
      <description>Our malfunctioning sense making organ is the fundamental sickness we can all be trying to heal.
We can measure our love based on our attention. Our attention is fundamental to our sense making. And so our love and our sense making are related individually and collectively.
 Love everyone  Love by proximity Love by relevance Be honest.    Love everyone. One of my claims is that a properly functioning sense making organ should be loving and able to prioritize information based on its relevance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap Federated Social Networking Protocol</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheap-federated-social-networking-protocol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/cheap-federated-social-networking-protocol/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Many people want to own their data and the algorithms which are used when engaging with other people on the internet. I mentioned this idea to a friend and he introduced me to Mastadon. I soon learned about activity pub and the fediverse.
I started thinking about how I want to use activity pub. I could join an existing Mastadon community or I could host my own server. I could also look at other open source projects which leverage activity pub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win My Vote in 2020</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-win-my-vote-in-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-win-my-vote-in-2020/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking about who I should vote for POTUS in 2020.
I would vote for the candidate who abandons the mainstream and supports new platforms for information distribution and sense making. Twitter and Facebook are aweful. And I don&amp;rsquo;t think the candidate should just go over to Parler. Ideally the POTUS would use an open source Mastadon server or some other federated social media platform which allows for decentralization and owning your own data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data and Environmental Policy Response</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/data-and-environmental-policy-response/</guid>
      <description>This is a response to Aaron Harburg&amp;rsquo;s Data and Environmental Policy.
 Environmental Law is predicated on the assumption that the government can effectively motivate its citizens to perform or abstain from certain activities.
 All laws which criminalize behavior are coercive and part of the failing justice system.
 The question is how incentives and punishments should be used to achieve and ensure the greatest effect.
 That’s a good question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and Government</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 08:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</guid>
      <description>What is religion? I like the meaning of the word religion which corresponds with the idea that Jordan Peterson introduced me to regarding our actions. When asked if he believes in God, he responds that he lives his life as if God exists. I think our actions are the essential part of our religious belief. I think it was the Christian James who taught faith without works is dead. I think our work is vital and defines our religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Card Payments</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/secure-card-payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/secure-card-payments/</guid>
      <description>My wife checked our bank account this morning and discovered that our debit card had been used by a thief. I verified that the card was in my wallet. I called my bank and cancelled the card so that the thief would not be able to use it again. And I created a dispute for the charge on my bank&amp;rsquo;s website.
My first thought was that the merchant should be responsible for this kind of thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Space Elevator</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/building-a-space-elevator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/building-a-space-elevator/</guid>
      <description>Introduction this post has been edited
The space elevator is a kind of structure which connects the surface of a large gravitational body with space. The tallest buildings on Earth are not space elevators and there are challenges we face when we construct tall buildings. I have discovered an architecture for overcoming these engineering challenges which divides the load using partitioning.
The tallest structure possible must make use of forces like buoyancy which oppose gravity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failing Justice Systems</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/failing-justice-systems/</guid>
      <description>I have always felt repulsed by rules which cause harm to people who are not causing harm. I think everyone should feel safe in a world where I carefully and illegally drive through an intersection when the light is red. There is no reason for the traffic camera to be used to mail me a ticket which could culminate in a shooting between myself and a law enforcer because I am unwilling to cooperate with a justice system which causes harm to good people disobeying bad laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Humans</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/managing-humans/</guid>
      <description>I have completed the first part of Managing Humans by Michael Lopp. I think the most interesting chapter in the book is titled &amp;ldquo;Titles are Toxic&amp;rdquo;. Lopp suggests titles are toxic because they attempt to place value on humans who are beautiful snowflakes. He thinks titles are as useless as business cards and resumes. And I tend to agree with his sentiment.
A general problem I see in organizations is that people keep their role if they are “good enough”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement with Eric Weinstein and Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement-with-eric-weinstein-and-peter-thiel/</guid>
      <description>How do people with good ideas and without power teach people with power who could best help make the ideas into our reality when there is no obvious way to even begin the conversation? People with good ideas and motivations need to be able to see a gate which can be opened for them and the paths which lead to that gate. What I have been trying to do is imagine gates and paths by which I am able to reach, teach, and learn with other people who are willing and able to solve important problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Encounter Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/how-to-encounter-disagreement/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this with Eric Weinstein in mind. But this general approach to learning and cooperating with a large community can be implemented by anyone who has a sufficiently large following. I am excited to see people trying to figure out how to improve the sense making organ for a large community of people.
You have realized that you need to put forth some effort having conversations with new people who have new ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ending the War on Drugs</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/ending-the-war-on-drugs/</guid>
      <description>Why was the War on Drugs started? If I steelman the arguments for the idea of controlling substances, I would imagine a different time without the internet when people had access to less information. I am young enough to remember researching cannabis and psilocybin on the internet before I experimented with those substances. There was a time when it was much harder to do your research in order to understand a substance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/disagreement/</guid>
      <description>Facebook doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a thumbs down reaction. And even if it did have a thumbs down reaction that reaction could get lost in the noise of other reactions. A disagreement is potentially the most valuable signal of all because it is an opportunity for learning to take place.
When I share this post on the internet with you it is an invitation to a discussion so that learning may take place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Philosophy Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-philosophy-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-philosophy-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>The value of work is related to all the costs and benefits of the work including the externalities. The usefulness of knowledge is based on its relationship with work. My economics knowledge has not been useful because I have never been in a position where my ignorance on the subject would be costly. My ability to obtain useful and valuable knowledge is dependent on my ability to recognize which kinds of knowledge are not useful to me at that point in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Economics Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-economics-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-economics-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>When I write about a world without hunger curi (Elliot Temple) wonders what I know about economics.
The Basics There is a supply of goods and services. There is demand for those goods and services. The prices of goods and services are related to supply and demand. If a good or service is scarce the price can be higher than when that same good or service is abundant assuming all other variables like demand are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A World Without Hunger</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/a-world-without-hunger/</guid>
      <description>The first person I have known to take autonomous agriculture technology seriously is Douglas Mallette, founder of Cybernated Farm Systems.
We can technically feed the world with autonomous agriculture technology which eventually requires no human labor.
It has been said that you can give a man a fish and feed him for a day. It has been said that you can teach a man to fish and feed him the rest of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Paths Forward Policy</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 07:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/my-paths-forward-policy/</guid>
      <description>My Policy I am willing to spend over 1 hour per day on average having public conversations with people on the internet. You can join my discord server.
If you ask me a publicly visible question, I will eventually respond. I will usually respond within 48 hours. If I don&amp;rsquo;t respond within 48 hours, do not hesitate to ask the question again and try to mention my username specifically to help get my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Resource Problem</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/human-resource-problem/</guid>
      <description>The Human Resource Problem Humans have the potential to solve many big problems which are not currently being solved. For example, we could eventually be living in a world where malnutrition and starvation is avoidable. The main reason we live in a world where humans suffer from malnutrition is because humans have not figured out how to work together effectively. I have broadly called this general problem of humans not working together effectively &amp;ldquo;HRP&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telework Experience</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 09:18:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/telework-experience/</guid>
      <description>When telework is done with the right tools and processes, it is far more efficient and effective than working on site.
Whether you are new to remote work or you have been doing it for years, I am confident that there is something we can do to reduce costs and increase the effectiveness of your organization through telework.
I have accumulated about 6 years of telework experience since graduating from Auburn University in 2008.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
