<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>religion on HeroLFG</title>
    <link>https://herolfg.com/tags/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in religion on HeroLFG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://herolfg.com/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract for the Web</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/contract-for-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/contract-for-the-web/</guid>
      <description>I think Tim Berners-Lee and I agree that we should try to use technology to help as many people as possible. And my impression is that he has done good work with his mind. I just watched The World Wide Web - A Mid-Course Correction where Tim recommends a contract for the web.
My hope was that Tim would be interested in a web where people may choose to sacrifice their anyonymity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarianism is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 06:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/utilitarianism-is-wrong/</guid>
      <description>The truth is that very few people are correct in their ideology because they do not understand human nature and our universal fallibility.
 I was a utilitarian when I was young. This means that I believed the means justify the ends. I would tell a lie if I could justify it. But I also know that I believed things which were wrong. I believed I had discovered a perpetual energy design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom and Security</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/freedom-and-security/</guid>
      <description>I will criticize an immoral Republican view and then I will criticize an immoral Democrat view. My morality assessments depend on whether or not a person&amp;rsquo;s behavior is in alignment with my ideology.
Introduction In a dream I am given a test. If everyone in the class picks the first choice then everyone gets a perfect score. But if anyone picks the second choice and does all the work then everyone who did the first choice will get half of a perfect score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christian</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/the-christian/</guid>
      <description>I am not convinced that being Christian is the best. My concern about Christians is that they are ultimately willing to sacrifice their life on Earth because their reward is in heaven. The Christian is at odds with the Anti-Christian who does not want to sacrifice their life on Earth because they do not believe their reward is in heaven.
Translation of Jesus&amp;rsquo; Teachings on the Mount You may as well inject the words &amp;ldquo;what if&amp;rdquo; in front of each sentence that follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misinterpretations</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/misinterpretations/</guid>
      <description>We humans let ideas and interpretations of words slip into our mind without thinking critically. And if we are not willing to question our beliefs then we remain stuck with ignorance and confusion. But if we question our beliefs then we have the opportunity to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Sense Making</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 05:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/love-and-sense-making/</guid>
      <description>Our malfunctioning sense making organ is the fundamental sickness we can all be trying to heal.
We can measure our love based on our attention. Our attention is fundamental to our sense making. And so our love and our sense making are related individually and collectively.
 Love everyone  Love by proximity Love by relevance Be honest.    Love everyone. One of my claims is that a properly functioning sense making organ should be loving and able to prioritize information based on its relevance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religion and Government</title>
      <link>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 08:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://herolfg.com/posts/morality-and-government/</guid>
      <description>What is religion? I like the meaning of the word religion which corresponds with the idea that Jordan Peterson introduced me to regarding our actions. When asked if he believes in God, he responds that he lives his life as if God exists. I think our actions are the essential part of our religious belief. I think it was the Christian James who taught faith without works is dead. I think our work is vital and defines our religion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>